真不错  我们买了辆
Oh, great. we've got the Prius that can
能预订餐厅  买电影票
make dinner reservations, buy movie tickets,
预报天气的丰田普锐斯
tell us the weather.
我只想要一辆门能打得开的车
I just want one that opens.
也许我们该买那辆
Maybe we should've got that one.
米奇尔
Mitchell!
天呐  泰迪
Oh, oh, my God! Teddy!
小卡  这是泰迪
Cam, this is Teddy.
泰迪  泰迪  泰迪
Teddy, Teddy, Teddy.
医生  泰迪医生
Doc--Doctor Teddy!
泰迪是米奇在我之前的
Teddy was Mitch's one significant
一个比较重要的男友
boyfriend before me.
那时米奇刚出柜
Uh, Mitch had recently just come out.
就如他自己说的
And as he put it,
一个人如果不爱自己  就很难爱上别人
it was hard to love someone else if he couldn't love himself.
我真说过那种话吗
I actually said those words?
现在倒是很难爱我自己了
Ugh. It's kind of hard to love myself right now.
当年是你说  "我需要点时间
You were the one who said, "I need some time.
我疗好心伤后会再联系你的"
I'll call you when I heal more."
一晃都过去十年了
Ten years later...
我从没那么说过
I never said that.
需要时间疗伤  真是甜蜜又敏感啊
Time to heal more! That's so sweet and sensitive.
你为什么要扼杀掉这种天性
Why did you kill that part of yourself?
我这周末要为医院举办一个募捐集会
You know, I'm hosting a fund-raiser for the hospital this weekend
就在南大街的旱冰场
at that roller rink on South Main.
你们能来吗
Any chance you guys can come?
-当然  -可能吧
- Yeah. Absolutely. - Possibly.
-我们一定去  -好吧
- We'll be there. - Okay.
太好了  周六4点见
Great. So 4:00 Saturday.
我真的很高兴碰到你们
I'm so glad I bumped into y'all.
我们也是  说再见  莉莉
Us, too. Say bye, Lily!
再见  莉莉
Bye, Lily.
我教她这样说的
I taught her that, so...
-再见  莉莉  -再见  泰迪
- Bye, Lily. - Bye. Bye, Teddy.
天呐  他人真不错
Oh, my gosh, he's great!
你不介意跟我前男友共度周末吗
You're okay making plans with my ex-boyfriend?
不介意  都过去那么久了
Um, yes. It's been a hundred years.
而且这也是当基佬的众多好处之一
Plus, this is one of the many benefits of being gay.
我们能跟前任做朋友
We can be friends with our exes
而不像直男直女们那样
without all the petty jealousy
饱受妒火的煎熬
straight people go through.
我跟胡娇算是朋友  所以
Well, I guess I am friends with Pepper, so...
我只跟胡娇约会过一次  就一次
I went on one date with Pepper. One.
你什么时候才能不提这茬
When are you gonna stop bringing it up?
你反应不这么激烈的时候
When you stop reacting like that.
爸爸爱胡娇
Daddy loves Pepper.
我教她的
I taught her that.
那是隐私
That's private.
抱歉  但为什么上面列了我们的名字
Oh, sorry. But why do you have all of our names down on a list?
为了写作文
It's for my school essay--
要求是在家人中选一个英雄
pick a hero in your family
并写出你为什么选择他
and write about why you've chosen him or her.
你还是有望入选的
You're still in the running,
但我不喜欢你照看我弟弟时喝葡萄酒
But I'm not loving that you're drinking wine while watching my brother.
是你家冰箱里有一瓶已经打开了的酒
Well, it was from an open bottle of white in your fridge, so...
这事关判断力  克莱尔
It's about judgment, Claire.
现在不是70年代了  我们都有常识的
It's not the 70's. We know better.
瓶子上有口红印
There was lipstick on the bottle.
我的宝贝们
There are my babies!
-晚餐怎么样  -非常完美
- How was dinner? - Perfect.
我吃了一份牛排  还有一些冰淇淋
I had a steak, I had some ice cream,
歌洛莉亚在她的鱼里发现了一根头发
Gloria found a hair in her fish,
结果餐厅给我们免单了
and it didn't cost us a penny!
也可能是我自己的头发
It might have been my own hair,
但杰很高兴我什么也没说
but Jay was so happy that I didn't say anything.
怎么了
What?
乖女儿  你走之前能抽点空吗
Honey, you got a second before you go?
我想跟你说点事
I wanna talk to you about something.
好吧  她为什么那样对我笑
All right. Why is she smiling at me like that?
是个好消息
It's good news.
好吧
Okay.
你记得我办公室的鲍勃吗
You remember Bob from my office?
记得啊  鲍勃叔叔  他变魔术
Yeah, uncle Bob. The one who did the trick
从我的耳朵里拿出一枚25分硬币
where he pulled a quarter out of my ear.
他后来又学了个魔术
He learned another trick.
从我们的养老金里掏走了5万美元
He pulled 50 grand out of our pension fund.
我把他炒了
Oh. I fired him.
但最糟糕的是
But the worst part is,
我当时正培养他接管公司
I was grooming him to take over the company.
但这事也有好的一面
But there's an upside.
他想让你为他工作
He wants you to work for him.
我知道现在只是普通工作而已
I know it's just a job right now,
但你知道他胸腔里不知得了什么毛病
but you know that he has this thing going on in his chest,
所以说不准什么时候
so you never know where
你就上位了  克莱尔
you're going to end up, Claire.
歌洛莉亚  我只是感冒而已
Gloria. Gloria, it's a cold.
总之  听着
Anyway, look,
我知道你一直想回归职场
I know you've been wanting to get back out there,
而我总是觉得  你要是重新开始工作
and I always kind of thought that if you did go back to work,
就该来跟我一块儿干
you'd come back to work with me.
我20年前在那里工作过半个暑假而已
I-I worked there for half a summer 20 years ago.
那时你干得非常棒  乖女儿
And it-- it was terrific, honey.
听我说  显然  我们会慢慢培养你
Listen, obviously, we'll start you out slow.
给你时间去重新了解这个公司
We'll give you time to re-learn about the place,
然后再提拔你  你是认识个关键人物的
and then maybe move you up. You know, you do know a guy.
他说的是他
He means him!
这机会太棒了  老爸  谢谢
It's a wonderful opportunity, dad. Thanks.
我能  我能考虑一下
Could I--could I think about it,
-问问菲尔的意见吗  -当然
- talk to Phil? - Oh, sure.
-我明天再打给你  -好好好
- I'll call you tomorrow. - All right. All right. All right.
-我儿子呢  还我儿子  -儿子还你
- Where's my boy? Give me my boy. - Here's your man.
小家伙还给你  真爱他
Here's your little man. Oh, love him.
关于这种"花"毯子我是怎么说的
What did I say about these flowered blankets for him?
把他扮得越来越像那位"花花公子"了
He's starting to take after Hugh Hef-nerd over there.
非常好笑  杰
Very amusing, Jay.
就让我把你的名字从这里划掉吧
Let me just get your name down here.
又是社区大学寄来的宣传册
Another brochure from a community college.
我赌这些都是老妈让他们寄来的
You know, I bet mom is having them send these.
是吗  你不觉得他们已经将你
Really? You don't think they've targeted you
锁定为必须招收的对象了吗
as a must-have recruit?
至少这一份没有矫揉造作的
At least this one doesn't have that fakey lunchtime shot
黑人亚裔妞儿印度人一起吃午餐的照片
of the black guy, asian girl, and an indian--
等一下  在这儿呢
Oh, wait! There it is.
那坐轮椅的孩子把其他人都逗乐了
Wow, that wheelchair kid is really cracking everybody up.
闺女们  你们的妈妈就要带晚餐回来了
girls, your mom's on her way home with dinner!
就当我从没收到过这个
I never got this.
要是被他看见  又要找我谈话了
If he sees it, we'll have to talk about it.
怎么了
What?
什么怎么了
What what?
如果外公打电话来  就说我不在家
If grandpa calls, I'm not home.
怎么了
What happened?
他想让我为他工作
He wants me to work for him.
培养我接管他的生意什么的
Like, groom me to take over or something.
我不知道该怎么拒绝
I don't know how I'm gonna say no.
你为什么要拒绝
Why would you say no?
你不是正要找工作吗
I thought you were looking for something.
而且我们也能增加收入啊
We could use the money, too,
尤其是万一海莉决定回去念书的话
especially if Haley decides to go back to school.
她还是把那些学校的宣传册都扔掉吗
Oh, is she still throwing out those college brochures?
刚才还扔了一份
Just tossed one now.
她以为是谁在负责倒垃圾啊
Who does she think empties the trash?
知道最惨的是什么吗
You know what really sucks?
那份工作本来挺不错的
That job could be great.
但我爸是个糟糕的老板  他太刻薄了
But my dad is a terrible boss. He is so mean.
"大小姐  咖啡壶是不会给自己洗澡的"
"Princess, coffeepot's not gonna wash itself."
原来你是从他那里学的
That's where you got that?
我就跟你说过一次
I said it to you one time.
那你直接告诉他好了  开诚布公
Well, you just gotta tell him straight up, man to man.
开诚布"母"  你的身材真棒
Woman to man. You're very shapely.
我知道  我会说的
I know. I will.
我只是非常讨厌那种感觉
It's just I hate it so much.
我让他非常失望的那4次
The--the four big times that I disappointed him,
让我很难受
it devastated me.
第一次是我剪短了我的头发
I mean, the first time, I cut off all my hair.
我去了别的州上大学
I went to college out of state.
我把他的复古车撞到了墙上
I crashed his vintage jag into a wall.
才三次啊
That's only three.
孩子们  吃饭了
Kids, dinner!
已经开始爱上这个了
Oh, loving this already.
如果没人摔成脑震荡的话
If no one gets a concussion,
我们一定会再来的
we're totally coming back.
听着  如果你觉得看到我和泰迪在一起
So listen, if at any point you're not okay
有什么不舒服的感觉
with seeing me and Teddy together,
就直接告诉我  我们可以走的
just please let me know, and we can go.
好的  谢谢你  如果你觉得
Oh, well, thank you. And if at any point
我对这事如此坦然  让你有些不舒服的话
you're not okay with me being so okay with it,
你也要告诉我
you let me know.
泰迪  泰迪  你好
Teddy! Teddy! Hey!
看看你
Aw, look at you!
这件T恤太美了  你真可爱
This shirt is fantastic. You're adorable.
你更可爱
You're adorable!
我觉得有人被迷住喽
Oh, I think somebody has a crush!
非常感谢你请我们来
Thank you so much for having us.
我都分不出我的两个妞儿谁更兴奋了
I don't know which one of my girls is more excited.
好了  过来  我们给你找双旱冰鞋
okay. Come on, let's get you some skates.
我想让泰迪一起来
I want Teddy to come.
亲爱的  我想泰迪一定还有别的事
Oh, honey, I-I'm sure Teddy has other things--
没关系  你们去吧  叙叙旧
No, no! You guys go! Catch up.
-我先穿鞋  -好的
- I'll lace up. - Okay.
可以走了吗
Okay, ready?
-玩开心点  -小卡舅夫
- Have fun, okay! - Hey, uncle Cam!
我的天  怎么回事
Oh, my gosh! Hey! What's--what's going on?
你们怎么会在这里
What--what are you guys doing here?
-泰迪邀请我们来的  -你们认识泰迪
- Teddy invited us. - You guys know Teddy.
-那是当然  -没错  泰迪棒极了
- Yeah, totally. - Yeah, Teddy's great.
注意了  业余爱好者们
Heads up, amateurs!
摇滚时间到  你们听到了没
It's time to rock 'n' roll! Do you get it?
小卡  你在这里做什么
Cam, what are you doing here?
见鬼  爸爸来了
Oh, hell, it's dad.
谁爸爸  不是你爸爸吧
Whose dad? Not your dad.
我一整天都没接他的电话
I have been avoiding his calls all day.
-快  菲尔  把我推远点  -走你
- Quick, Phil, slingshot me. - All right.
孩子们  林波舞滑法[后仰穿过横杆]
Oh. Limbo skate, kids.
你的身段能放多低
How low can you go?
周六晚上  我居然和家人在
I'm at a roller rink with my family
旱冰场玩  还能更低吗
on a Saturday night. I win.
我得给莉莉照张相
I have got to get a photo of Lily.
泰迪把她逗得前仰后合的
Teddy's making her giggle so hard.
人人都爱...泰迪
Oh, well, everybody loves... Teddy, so...
但你要是介意的话  就告诉我
But you'll let me know if you're not okay.
米奇尔  你知道你全家人都被你前男友
Mitchell, do you know your entire family's here,
邀请来了吗
invited by your ex-boyfriend?
菲尔和克莱尔  杰和歌洛莉亚
Phil and Claire, Jay and Gloria,
还有你堂兄皮特
your cousin Pete.
小卡  这是场募捐活动  好吗
C--it's a-- it's a fund-raiser, all right?
我想他一定是把自己所有联系人都请来了
I'm sure he just invited everyone on his contact list.
那倒是能说得通
Oh, well, that makes sense.
是啊  当然了
Yes, of course it does.
还有  我受宠若惊
and... I'm flattered.
为什么你会受宠若惊
Why are you flattered?
-你懂的啦  -我不懂
- You know. - I don't.
你懂的
You do!
我真不懂
I really don't!
歌洛莉亚  穿上溜冰鞋跟我去冰上旋转
Gloria, throw on those skates and take a whirl with me.
我非常想去
Oh, I totally would,
但我在照顾莉莉  她不想滑冰
but I'm taking care of Lily and she doesn't want to.
我想滑
Oh. Yes, I do.
不  你不想  你之前告诉过我的
No, you don't. You told me before.
你不记得了吗  我怎么会撒谎呢
You don't remember? Why would I lie?
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.
你不会滑旱冰
You don't know how to roller-skate.
我当然会了  我没什么不会的
Of course I do. I know how to do everything.
对着你我真是撒不了谎
I can't lie to that face.
幸好我嫁的人不是你
It's a good thing that we're not married.
我不...
Well, I don't...
我不会滑冰  我是个优雅的女子
I can't skate. I am an elegant woman.
那意味着我永远也不去做
That means that I never do
那少数几件我做得不太完美的事情
the few things that I don't really do that good.
可我是个天生的滑冰老师
But I'm a natural teacher.
但我会看起来很蠢
But I'm going to look stupid.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria...
相信我
Trust me.
只要站在我身边
As long as you're standing next to me,
你就不会看起来很蠢
you will not look stupid.
太好了  都没地方坐了
Oh, thank god! There is no place to sit.
我总会给亲爱的侄女们留位置的
Always room at my table for my darling nieces.
被你们先抢了
Uhh... You beat us to it.
我们正准备问这小孩能不能一起坐呢
We were gonna ask this kid if we could share.
他就要走了
Well, he was just leaving.
你们完全可以过来一起坐
Yeah, you can totally sit with us.
我当时甚至不想把你们两个写进名单
You know, I debated even putting you two on here.
漂亮哦
Whoa, fancy.
我知道  我可是曾在这里工作过的
Yeah, I know. Well, I did used to work here.
等等  你是洗手间墙上照片里那个克莱尔
W-w-wait. You're the Claire from the bathroom?
那照片还在呢
Oh, is it still here?
是的
Y-yeah... oh...
看看你俩  多年未见
Oh! Hey! Look at you two catching up
-聊得真欢乐  -没那么久
- after all these years. - Well, it hasn't been that long.
也就一个月前  艾丽克斯得了流感
It's been like a month since you came by
-他还来过呢  对吧  -没开玩笑吧
- when Alex had the flu, right? - Oh, no kidding!
我还在她家吃了顿家常饭呢
Well, I do get a home-cooked meal out of it.
而且我欠他们个人情
Plus I owe these guys.
我最近两次买房  菲尔帮了不少忙
Phil helped me buy my last two houses.
真棒  多好的一段故事
Oh. So good. Such great stories.
-是啊  -叫你呢
- Yeah. - Hey, you!
你怎么不给我回电话
You owe me a phone call!
我知道  我会打给你的
I know! I'm gonna call you!
泰迪在这里
Hey! Teddy's here, huh?
你个赖账的  打高尔夫还欠我50块呢
Hey, you deadbeat, you owe me 50 bucks for the golf.
等你下次前列腺检查时我再塞给你
Well, maybe I'll slip it to you during your next prostate exam.
我打赌你就盼着那天了  小变态
I'll bet you're counting the days, you perv.
真有趣啊
Oh. So funny.
你和杰还真有话说呀  是吧
You and Jay really seem to have a thing, don't ya?
你和歌洛莉亚关系怎么样
And Gloria--what's the nature of your relationship with her?
事实上  我们今晚第一次见面
Well, actually, we just met tonight.
我不是很确定她喜不喜欢我
You know, I'm not so sure she likes me.
真的吗
Really?
我是说  她需要点时间才能熟络
Uh, well, I mean, she just takes a little time to warm up.
谢谢  也谢谢你今晚能过来
Oh, thanks. And thank you, again, for coming tonight.
利用筹集的这些钱  我们可以
With the money we raised, we'll be able
给4千多个有需要的孩子接种疫苗
to inoculate over 4,000 needy kids
抵御一些非常可怕的疾病
against some truly awful diseases.
你跟卢克关系怎么样
And how well do you know Luke?
我也喜欢那部电影
I love that movie, too!
在上海摩天大楼上的那场打斗戏太帅了
Yeah, that cool fight scene on that skyscraper in Shanghai--
让我好想去日本
It really made me want to go to Japan.
为什么  上海在中国
Why? Shanghai's in China.
我是说  你可不想飞到日本
I'm just saying, you don't want to fly to Japan,
然后打车说  "送我去上海市中心"
get in a cab and say, "Take me to downtown Shanghai."
那可太贵了
It's a pretty expensive ride.
我要去趟厕所
Uh, um, I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
跟我一起去
Come with me.
马上回来哦  帅哥们
Be right back, guys.
你在干什么
Uh, what do you think you're doing out there?
-我在勾搭啊  -这就是我担心的
- I'm flirting. - That's what I was afraid of.
我可不会为了让一个男生喜欢我
Look, I'm not gonna pretend I'm stupid
-就故意装傻  -当然不
- just so a boy will like me. - Of course not.
但你不一定要贬低那可怜的男孩
But you don't have to put the poor guy to shame.
勾搭男人是要增加你自己的魅力
Flirting with boys is about increasing your value,
不是去打压他们
not decreasing theirs.
真是复杂  你在哪本杂志里学到的
That's a complicated thought. What magazine taught you that?
你又来了  又贬低他人
You're doing it again! The mean thing.
你自己有没有意识到啊
Can you even hear it or what?!
-我意识到了  -好
- I heard it. - Good.
现在他知道你很聪明了
So now that he knows that you're smart,
我们来试着表现得温柔些
let's work on being nice.
-把帽衫脱掉好吗  -不
- Wanna ditch the hoodie? - No.
没事没事  慢慢来
That's all good. It's a process.
哥们  在这家里想找出个英雄很难吧
Man, tough finding a hero in this family, huh?
我自己也有很多麻烦事
You know, I've got problems of my own.
我不可能总是配合你演出
I can't always be the lovable sidekick on "The Manny show."
你难道没有发现我在暴饮暴食吗
Did you even notice I'm binge-eating?
看来你真的有心事
You're really going through something.
想谈谈吗
Wanna talk about it?
一点也不想
Not even a little bit.
也别像往常一样烦我
And don't go hounding me like you always do.
多谢你重建我对这个家庭的信心
Well, thanks for restoring my faith in this family.
我要是泰迪的亲戚就好了
Too bad I'm not related to Teddy.
-他这人似乎很棒  -可不是嘛
- He seems terrific. - Doesn't he, though?
屈膝
Knees bent.
放松手臂  挺胸
Arms loose. Chin up.
提臀
Butt out.
不行  菲尔  太难了
Ay, no, Phil. This is too much.
记住口诀  "屈松挺提"
No, just remember, "Kbalcubo."
屈  松  挺  提
K-b-a-l-c-u-b-o.
就是"屈膝放松手臂挺胸提臀"
"Koala bears always lose cherries under big overpasses."
这么长  我怎么记得住啊
Ay, no! How am I gonna remember all that?!
我扶住你了
I gotcha.
泰迪  你真帅呆了
Ay, Teddy... Teddy, you're amazing!
谢谢你救了我
Thank you for saving me!
小子  让一让  让我来一拳
Let me get in there, boys. Excuse me.
走你
Boom!
好啦
Okay!
好啦  是时候聊聊了
Okay, clearly it's time to talk.
小卡  你显然是生气了
All right, Cam, Cam, you're obviously upset.
但你要相信我
But trust me--
我和泰迪绝对没有藕断丝连
there are no lingering feelings between me and Teddy.
我才不在乎你和泰迪的事
I don't care about you and Teddy.
我是不喜欢他和你们家人藕断丝连
I don't like what's lingering between him and your family.
-什么  -米奇尔  你看看
- What? - Mitchell, look around.
你家人都在背叛我  和你的前男友厮混
Your family is cheating on me with your ex-boyfriend.
背叛  好吧  他们的关系确实
Cheating--okay, yes. Th-there is a bit more contact
比我知道的要更亲密一点  但是
between them than I realized, but--
是嘛  你又要怪我太敏感
Oh, o-oh, yeah. Now this is where we make Cam
怪我小题大做了
the over-sensitive drama queen.
就是不能为了我做出些改变
God forbid we take any action to make things right for me.
好好好  那你想要我怎么做
Well, okay, okay. Okay, what do you want me to do?
要我叫他们跟泰迪"分手"吗
Would you like me to ask them to break up with Teddy?
你是想让我这么做吗
Is that what you're asking?
当然不是  我绝不会提那种要求
Of course not. I would never ask that.
-那样也太疯狂了  -那就好
- That would be insane. - Well, good.
我如果那样要求  就太疯狂了
It would be as insane for me to ask that
但你主动提出来  就非常识趣
as it would be sane for you to offer it.
所以你就是要我那么做
So that is what you're asking.
不  我才没要你那么做
No, that's what I'm not asking.
但如果你要那么做  我希望你是自愿的
But if you decide to do it, I want it to come from you,
而不是我逼你的
Not me,
因为我显然没有那样要求你
because I'm clearly not asking for it.
-好吧  真是无理取闹  -是吗
- Okay, this is nuts. - Is it?
我千方百计  辛辛苦苦
I worked my fingers to the bone
讨你家的老顽固们的欢心
to get these jumpy protestants to love me,
现在却发现  他们和你的前男友
and now I find out they're holding a torch
打得火热  不可开交
for the man who came before me?
我不是无理取闹  我很痛心
It's not nuts. It's actually quite painful.
先生  打扰一下  您得奖了
Excuse me, sir? You just won a prize
您刚刚在拳击游戏机上创造了新记录
for setting a rink record on the boxing machine.
可以给您照张相
If you wouldn't mind taking a picture
贴在我们的光荣榜上吗
for our wall of fame?
当然可以  我一会儿就来
Oh, yeah, sure. Absolutely. Just one second.
开心吧
That's exciting.
米奇尔  我知道你会做正确的事
Mitchell, I know you'll do what's right.
除非你喜欢看着我受辱
Unless you like seeing me humiliated.
谢谢
Thank you.
菲尔  大家都在盯着我
Everybody was staring, Phil.
要不我们到外面没人能看见的地方练习
Well, what if we practice outside where no one can see us?
我都紧张得打嗝了
Ay, and now I have the nervous burps!
克莱尔
Oh... Claire.
爸  你在这儿干嘛
Dad? Wh-what are you doing out here?
显然这是今晚找你聊聊的唯一办法
Apparently this is the only way we'll get to talk tonight.
关于工作的事
About this job.
同志们
Hey, guys.
好像有要紧事  爸  等会儿聊
This sounds really important, dad. Hang on.
米奇尔  你继续
Go ahead, Mitchell.
听我说  这是我本人的想法
Okay, so listen. This is coming from me.
没人逼我  我需要你们帮个忙
No one else. But I need you to do something,
-而且我不想你们吐槽我  -老天爷
- And I don't want you to give me any flack. - Oh, jeez.
你这就是在吐槽  我觉得你们
That's flack. I-I think it's a little weird
还和泰迪那么亲近很奇怪
how you all still hang out with Teddy so much...
我早说嘛
Told you.
我觉得  你们以后最好还是
And I think it'd be appropriate if maybe you all,
别再跟他来往了
you know, stopped seeing him.
这话是小卡让你说的  对吧
This is coming from Cam, isn't it?
不  不是
No, it's not.
慢着
Wait a second.
小卡觉得我们不能同时喜欢他和泰迪吗
Cam doesn't think we can love him and Teddy at the same time?
而且你就这么出卖了小卡
And you just sold Cam out like that?
等等  那是什么
Wait. What is that?
我告诉你是什么  是悲剧
I'll tell you what it is. It's sad.
各位顾客  请别慌张
Hey, skaters! Not an emergency,
我们的小吃店发生了小火灾
but we do have a small fire in the snack bar.
请大家有秩序地离开现场  谢谢
We'd like everyone to calmly file outside. Thanks.
各位  出口在这边
Okay, everyone, the exit's over here.
大家往这边走
Come this way, please.
走这边出来吧
Hey, this way, to the exit.
来吧  大家快从这边出来
All right, everybody over here.
-快啊  -你们帮帮我吧
- Come on. - You guys, just do this for me.
可是他离我们那么远
But... he's all the way over there.
你们"不用急"
There's no hurry.
我们可是在70年代建造的木建筑里
We're in a wooden box built in 1970.
-快走吧  -好  走吧
- Let's go! - Oh--all right, let's go.
谢谢你们  你们真"好"
Okay, thank you. That's very nice.
真是太"贴心"了
Sweet of you.
各位  好消息
Hey, skaters, good news!
火已经被扑灭了
Fire's out!
抱歉让你们受惊了
Sorry for the scare.
好啦好啦  先别生气
All right--all right, before you get upset,
这只是因为那边比较方便
this was just about convenience.
是吗
Was it?
还是在暗中向我表态
Or was it a perfect metaphor?
米奇尔  恭喜你
Congratulations, Mitchell.
这是我有生以来最难过的一次滑旱冰经历
This is the saddest I've ever been in roller skates.
小心点
Okay, be careful.
我不想受伤
I don't want to get hurt, okay?
-没人会受伤的  -抓紧我
- No one's gonna get hurt. - Hold on!
疼死我了
Aah! That hurts!
我们能不能
Okay, if we could just...
我"米"了个"奇"的
Son of a Mitchell!
一点也别担心
Do not worry one bit.
你就快学会了
You are gettin' it!
我们还是离车远点  行不
Let's get away from the cars, huh?
好恶心
Disgusting.
克莱尔·普里契特
Claire Pritchett?
-杰夫  -真的是你
- Jeff? - No way!
你从这里辞职后我就再没见过你
I haven't seen you since you worked here.
你  你还在这工作啊
You... you still do.
是的  做自己喜欢的工作
Yeah, do what you love,
-工作也就不再是苦差事了  对吧  -对
- you never work a day in your life, right? - Right.
碰到你太好了
This is perfect.
刚才有个人在溜冰场上吐了
Some civilian just yakked in the rink.
你能不能帮我照看一下柜台
Can you take over for a minute?
不能
Um... no.
这是我赚钱最多的地方
Ah, it's kind of where I make most of my money.
我不想把它关了
You know, I hate to shut it down.
我把一姑娘肚子搞大了  这事说来话长
Ah, I got a girl pregnant. It's a whole thing.
-好吧  我暂时照看一下  -太好了
- All right. I'll do it for a minute, sure. - Great.
-太谢谢你了  -行了
- Thank you. Thank you. - Okay.
-对了  -什么事
- Oh, hey... - Yeah?
我还在回味那个吻
I still think about that kiss.
老天啊
Oh, god.
太恶心了
Gross.
妈妈  我刚刚吐了
Mom, I threw up.
亲爱的  那人是你啊  你会没事的
Oh, honey, that was you? You're gonna be okay.
我来找点东西安抚一下你的肚肚
Let me get you something for your tummy.
我压力太大了
I'm just so stressed out.
你知道我要写的那篇英雄的作文吗
You know that hero essay I have to write?
爸爸想当然地以为我写的是他
Well, dad kind of assumed I wrote it about him...
但我没写他
But I didn't.
他现在要读我的作文
And now he wants to read it,
我不知道该怎么办
and I don't know what to do.
别担心你爸  我相信他会理解的
Don't worry about your father. I am sure he'll understand.
克莱尔  我来给卡梅隆拿点冰块
Claire, I need some ice for Cameron.
还有  我们得谈谈工作的事情
And we have to talk about the job.
除非你决定回到这里工作了
Unless you've taken back this one.
爸  我在招呼顾客呢
Dad, I'm with a customer right now.
马上就来跟你谈
I'll be with you in just a moment.
亲爱的  我会跟你爸爸谈
Honey, I'll talk to your dad.
你觉得他不会因为我写的是你而生气吧
You don't think he'll be upset I wrote it about you?
你写的是我吗
You wrote it about me?
妈妈  你知道我一般怎么做作业
Mom, you know me and homework.
我没太动脑子  什么是英雄
I didn't give it much thought. What's a hero?
一个无所畏惧的人
Someone who's not afraid of anything,
一个强大的人  那就是你啊
and who's strong-- that's you.
可爸爸也很棒
But dad's so great, too.
-我又要吐了  -好了好了
- Here it comes. - Okay. All right.
你赶紧坐下来  坐下  宝贝
You just sit down. Sit down, sweet pea.
把这个喝了  你会没事的
Have your drink. You're gonna be fine.
真心话时间到
Here goes. Um...
爸爸  上次我们一起工作的时候
So, dad, the last time we worked together,
-我们的关系很紧张  -什么
- it was tense between us. - What?
-没有啊  -有的
- No, it wasn't. - Yes, it was.
你对我非常严厉
You were--you're really hard on me,
你说话时居高临下
and you talk down to me.
-你又胡说八道了  -好吧
- You don't know what you're talking about. - Right.
当我和你当面对质时  就像现在这样
And when I confronted you, like I am doing now,
你无动于衷  就像你现在一样
you were insensitive, like you are being now.
我谢谢你给我这个机会
And while I really appreciate the opportunity,
我很爱你
and I do love you very much,
但我觉得我们最好不要一起工作
I don't think that working together is a very good idea.
好吧
All right, fine.
说实话  我很失望
I'm not gonna lie. I'm very disappointed.
-我们赢了  -太逊了
- We won! - Man, that sucks!
是啊  我们太没男子气概了
Yeah, totally un-masculating.
[正确表达是Emasculating]
至少你们玩的时候样子很酷
Well, at least you guys look cool when you play.
我们再玩一局  这局就当没发生
Let's play again. This never happened.
实际上  我们得去找我们的家人了
Actually, we need to go hang out with our family for a while.
真的吗  现在吗
Really? Now?
对  但我们不会走远  等会儿见
Yeah, but we'll be around. We'll see you guys.
怎么了  我又做错事了吗
What happened? Did I mess up?
-你做得很好  -那他不喜欢我吗
- No, you did great. - So he didn't like me?
-他可喜欢你了  -那我们干嘛要走开
- No, he totally liked you. - Then why'd we walk away?
他本来就不是重点
This was never about him.
这是为了给你增加点自信
This was about getting you some confidence.
男生们会意识到你这点的  更优秀的男生
Guys will pick up on that. Better guys.
那种即使输给女生
Guys who can lose to a girl
也不会觉得有损男子气概的人
without feeling e-masculated.
但愿你以后不会用我接下来的话反击我
Okay, try not to throw this in my face one day,
但我有时觉得你其实挺聪明
but sometimes you're actually really smart.
真正意义上的聪明  希望你知道
Like, smart smart. I hope you know that.
谢谢
Thanks.
我以后当然会拿这话来反击你
And I'm totally throwing that in your face one day.
你开玩笑呢吧
Are you kidding?
太感谢了  一切正常吗
Oh, thank you so much. Everything go okay?
不  我被困在柜台后面
No. Actually, I was trapped back here,
又跟我爸吵了一架
my dad and I got in a whole thing.
现在他生气了
now he's mad at me.
你在哪儿找到那个的
Whoa, where'd you find that?
我知道你把啤酒放在哪儿  杰夫
I know where you keep the beer, Jeff.
我太恨这感觉了
I hate this feeling!
我发誓  这从我12岁那年就开始了
I swear, it started when I was 12 years old
我在社会研究课考试中得了个C
and I got a "C" in social studies.
我爸看我的眼神  别人看到会以为
The way my dad looked at me, you would have thought
我穿着抹胸装去了教堂
I'd worn a tube top in church.
他知道我会非常伤心
He knew it crushed me.
他不在乎
He didn't care.
这就是我不能为他工作的原因
That's why I can't work for him.
他以前对我很严厉  现在也一样会
He was hard on me then. He's gonna be hard on me now.
告诉你  人是不会变的
I'm telling you, people don't change.
我改变了
I've changed.
我不想再忍受这些
I don't wanna put up with this stuff.
和20年前相比  我现在完全不一样了
I am a completely different person than I was 20 years ago.
孩子们  一共是18.5美元
All right, kids, that's gonna be $18.50.
收20
Out of $20?
找你1.5美元
There's your $1.50...
我想也是
I thought so.
我想说
Well, I mean,
你跟他说了实话  心里舒服些了吗
do you feel good that you were at least honest with him?
没有  想都别想
No. And... Super no.
因为每次我令他失望
Because I'm the one who's left with this awful feeling
深感愧疚的人却是我
every time I disappoint him.
这不公平
It's not fair.
做恶人的不是我
'cause I'm not the bad guy here.
他需要知道这点
He needs to know that.
怎么样
How's that?
-好些了吗  -好多了
- That better? - Yeah, much better.
谢谢你  泰迪
Thank you, Teddy.
你好了  和我去溜冰
You're fixed. Skate with me.
我觉得还没好到那种程度  宝贝
I think it's a little soon, sweetie.
不  我是叫泰迪
No. Teddy.
没问题  孩子
But--oh, sure thing, kiddo.
尽量冰敷  三天不要做侧手翻
Hey, lots of ice, no cartwheels for three days.
-好的  -准备好了吗  来吧
- Yeah. - Ready? Come on.
很好的小伙子
Good guy.
泰迪吗  是啊  他最好了
Who--Teddy? Yeah. Yeah, he's the best.
真不敢相信他居然找不到伴儿
Nuts he can't find anybody, huh?
肯定有什么问题
Gotta be something a little off there.
反正他没让米奇尔表现出最好的一面
He definitely did not bring out the best in Mitchell,
这点我能肯定
I can tell you that right now.
是吗
Oh, really?
并不是说这有什么关系
Well, you know, not that it matters...
不过能不能说具体些
but in what way exactly?
说实话  他们在一起的时候
Honestly? When they were together,
米奇尔相当令人头痛
Mitchell could be a bit of a pill.
我喜欢泰迪
Now, I like Teddy,
但他们分手时  其实我有些庆幸
but when they broke up, I was actually kinda glad.
当然了  米奇尔觉得
Of course, Mitchell thought that I was
我心里不舒服是因为不接受同性恋
uncomfortable because of the gay thing,
也许我当时是的  但是
and maybe I was, but...
我真的只是想让他开心
I really just wanted him to be happy.
像他现在这样
Like he is now.
你们在一起后  大家都想
And when you two started up, everyone thought,
就是他了
"Well, there it is."
孩子们  双人溜冰开始
Okay, kids. Couples skate.
拉上你爱的人  开溜吧
Grab someone you love and get out there.
杰  你真是...
Jay, you can be so...
-我不会和你溜冰的  小卡  -好吧
- I'm not skating with you, Cam. - Yeah.
我呢  爸  你要和我一起溜冰吗
What about me, dad? You wanna skate with me?
什么样的人才有资格被称为英雄
What qualifies someone as a hero?
显然  英雄必须是我们尊敬的人
Obviously, a hero has to be someone we respect.
我们敬仰的人
A person we look up to.
心胸宽广的人
A person who is generous of spirit.
愿意成长与学习的人
Who's willing to grow and learn.
爸
So... Dad,
如果提议还有效的话
if that offer still stands...
真的吗  为什么改变主意
Really? What changed?
有些事不同了
A couple of things.
也许是这世上你最爱的人
Maybe it's the person you love most in the world
或是尽力享受生活的人
or the guy who makes the most out of life,
不管别人怎么想
no matter what anyone thinks.
没事的  大家都在笑我
It's cool! No, everybody's laughing at me!
-继续溜  机会来了  -不
- Keep rolling! This is your chance! - No! No!
太好了
Yeah!
-菲尔  -我知道
- Phil! - I know!
-不过对我来说  -加油  爸
- For me, though... - Go, dad!
我家里的英雄就是我的家人
The hero in my family is my family,
我们在一起才是真英雄
because of who we are together.
C-
C-minus.
作业要求不是这样的
"This was not the assignment."
我告诉你谁不是我的英雄
I'll tell you who is not my hero.
丽塔·米克纳布老师
Mrs. Rita Mcnabb.
谢谢  谢谢
Oh, thank you! Thank you!
大家在看什么
What is everybody looking at?
我再说一次也没关系
Oh, I guess I can tell the story one more time.
是的  我当时正在生气
Sure, yeah. Well, I was mad about something.
我甚至不记得在气什么了
I don't even remember what.
我转过身  这一刻
I turned. Now at this point,
我更像是野兽  而不是人
I'm more animal than I am man.
猛击拳击游戏机
Strike the punching machine,
显然我是打破了什么世界纪录
and apparently I broke some sort of world record.
我想我永远不会忘记的就是
I guess the thing that I'll never forget
破纪录时游戏机发出的声音
is the sound that it made.
好像有敲钟声  口哨  汽笛
It was, like, bells and whistles and sirens.
不太可能描述清楚
It's impossible to describe.
不是吧
Oh, no!
这可是我生平打出的第一拳
That was literally the first punch I've ever thrown!
你这辈子都不准再见他了
You are never to see him again.
是  我知道
Yes, I know.